

## **My Contact**

- Paullevites84@gmail.com
- +234-8136286614
- paullevitesofficial.vercel.app

### **Skills**

- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- React
- Firebase
- Sass
- Nextjs
- Wordpress
- Material UI
- Redux
- Flux
- Enzyme

### **Education**

- University of Benin
   Bsc Computer Science
   currently enrolled
- ALXse
   Sof Engineering Backend
   2023 2024
- Havard CS50
   Computer science programming
   Completed in 2022
- Udemy Frontend Development Course Completed - 2022

# Paul Ifeoluwa-Levites

## Software Engineer

#### **About Me**

I am a Dedicated and detail-oriented Frontend Engineer with years of experience in frontend technology, with a goal to solve tech related problems in various institutions of the world.

This zealots has resulted in me working on various projects, as well as consulting for tech startups and educational bodies.

## **Professional Experience**

Heala Tech - Frontend Engineer intern

2022 June - 2023 June

Key responsibilities:

- · Test New builds to make sure it is bug free
- · Assisted the team leads on building new projects
- · Assistant project manager
- Worked with the product team as a go between product and tech team

Freelance - Tech Tutor

2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Explained the basics of Frontend technologies to tech enthusiasts
- collaborating with backend developers to work on tech projects to give to help in making students understand better.

Tech Edu - Frontend Tutor

2024 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- · Tasked with teaching the basics of frontend
- collaborating with backend developers to work on tech projects to give to help in making students understand better.
- Helped improve the website of the company

Freelancing - Frontend Developer/Project Manager

2023 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Brought together a team to take on freelancing jobs
- Worked as the frontend developer
- Developed Dynamic web applications for clients/users